Guide to the ethnic archives oral histories audio recordings 1966-1997
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
Ethnic archives oral histories audio recordings
1966-1997
University of Utah Libraries, Special Collections Audio Visual Archives Special Collections 295 South 1500 East Salt Lake City, Utah 84112-0860 (801) 581-8864
A0853
American West Center
321 compact discs and 42 reel-to-reel audiotapes.
The Ethnic Archives oral histories audio recordings (1966-1997) consists of interviews with individuals from various Utah communities. Groups represented include: Croatian, Greek, Spanish, Japanese, Mexican, Zuni, Paiute, other Native American communities, and women in Utah politics. The collection also features items about general Western history. The American West Center is dedicated to documenting the history of the intermountain region and surrounding areas.
Organizational History
The American West Center is a research center at the University of Utah which is affiliated with the College of Social and Behavioral Science. The Center is dedicated to providing educational and curricular support to Indian tribes, school districts, other interested organizations, and the general public through consultations, research, and publications.
The Ethnic Archives oral histories audio recordings (1966-1997) consists of interviews with individuals from various Utah communities. The interviews are divided into the following groups: Croatian oral histories, Greek oral histories, Spanish oral histories, Japanese-American research project, Japanese Asian studies oral histories, Utah women's political oral history project, Walker River oral histories, Mexico oral history project, Zuni land claim oral history project, Westwood oral history project, Krodel interviews, Walker River Paiute Tribe oral histories, Indian self-rule oral histories, McKay interviews and general Western materials.
The materials are arranged by ethnic group.
Materials must be used on-site; no use of original material, access copies will be made available for viewing. Five business days advanced notice required. Access to parts of this collection may be restricted under provisions of state or federal law, condition of the material, or by donor.
See also the Doris Duke American Indian oral history project audio recordings (A0001).
Utah--Emigration and immigration; Utah--Ethnic relations; Immigrants--Utah--Interviews; Children of immigrants--Utah--Interviews; Social Classes; Sound Recordings; Oral Histories; Sound recordings
- Croatian oral histories, 1972-1975
  - George Pezell, 1972 July 17; Compact disc (Disc C-1)
    Interviewed by J. Stipanovich
  - Tonka and Walter Bolic, 1972 August 14; Compact disc (Disc C-2)
  - John Dunoskovich, 1972 September 20; Compact disc (Disc C-3)
  - Matt Starr, 1973 January 12; Compact disc (Disc C-4)
  - Dr. Rasa Pirc, 1973 July 05; Compact disc (Disc C-5)
  - Mary Zagar Dupin, 1972 December 18; Compact disc (Disc C-6)
  - John Skerl, 1973 January 12; Compact disc (Disc C-7)
  - Joe and Bessie Chesnik, 1973 January 12; Compact disc (Disc C-8)
  - Tony Klarich, 1973 January 13; Compact disc (Disc C-9)
  - Martin Kramenich, 1973 January 13; Compact disc (Disc C-10)
  - Bessie and Joe Hinich, 1973 June 19; Compact disc (Disc C-11)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Mike Dragos, 1972 June 22; Compact disc (Disc C-12)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Ely Sasich, 1972 June 26; Compact disc (Disc C-13)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Joe Hinich, 1972 June 27; Compact disc (Disc C-14)
    Interviewed by J. Stipanovich and H. Papanikolas
  - Ely and Peter Klasna, 1972 July 07; Compact disc (Disc C-15)
  - Zora Bogdanovich, 1972 September 20; Compact disc (Disc C-16)
  - Pete Stapanovich, 1972 September 24; Compact disc (Disc C-17)
  - Joseph Church, 1972 October 28; Compact disc (Disc C-18)
  - Mayor Joseph Mazuran, 1972 November 28; Compact disc (Disc C-19)
  - Mike and Millie Dragos, 1972 November; Compact disc (Disc C-20)
  - Milka Smiljanich, 1972 December; Compact disc (Disc C-21)
    Interviewed by H. Papanikolas
  - Grey Melich, 1975 January 24; Compact disc (Disc C-22)
  - Joe Mikich (Disc C-23)
    Tape removed from collection March 13 2002.
  - John Cvar, 1973 January 31; Compact disc (Disc C-24)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Valentine Vouk, 1973 February 13; Compact disc (Disc C-25)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Marko Yellinich, 1973 February 14; Compact disc (Disc C-26)
  - Caroline Skerl, 1973 February 15; Compact disc (Disc C-27)
  - Katie Starr, 1973 February 15; Compact disc (Disc C-28)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Rudy Rebol, 1973 February 15; Compact disc (Disc C-29)
  - Caroline Tomsic and Raymond Toson, 1973 January 18; Compact disc (Disc C-30)
  - Mike Livoda, 1973 June 20; Compact disc (Disc C-31)
  - Frank and Caroline Tomsic, 1973 June 27; Compact disc (Disc C-32)
  - Dragica Busio, 1973 June 26; Compact disc (Disc C-33)
  - Nick Thomas, 1973 June 26; Compact disc (Disc C-34)
  - Joseph Miljak, 1973 June 26; Compact disc (Disc C-35)
  - Mrs. F. A. Davi, 1974 July 09; Compact disc (Disc C-36)
  - John Dunoskovi, 1974 July 09; Compact disc (Disc C-37)
  - Anica Susich and Violet Heath, 1974 July 17; Compact disc (Disc C-38)
  - Mary Truden, 1974 July 19; Compact disc (Disc C-39)
  - Vick Marinich, 1974 July 29; Compact disc (Disc C-40)
  - Angelina Teak, 1974 August 25; Compact disc (Disc C-41)
  - Mary Sobar, 1974 August 26; Compact disc (Disc C-42)
- Greek oral histories, 1969-1975
  - Mrs. Mageras, 1969 March 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-1)
    Interviewed by H. Papanikolas. This audiotape has not been digitized and may be of poor sound quality.
  - Louis Lingos, 1970 April 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-4)
    This audiotape has not been digitized and may be of poor sound quality.
  - Rolla West, 1970 May 21; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-6)
  - Rolla West and Mr. Fryer, 1970 May 21; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-7)
  - Harry G. Metos, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-9)
    Interviewed by H. Papanikolas and Theodore Papanikolas. This audiotape has not been digitized and may be of poor sound quality.
  - Mrs. John (Leona) Papoulis, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-12)
  - Mrs. William J. Pappas, 1972 July 11; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-19)
    Interviewed by H. Papanikolas and Gerogia Angelos. This audiotape has not been digitized and may be of poor sound quality.
  - George P. Lamb, 1972 September; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-20)
    Interviewed by H. Papanikolas and Georgia Angelos. This audiotape has not been digitized and may be of poor sound quality.
  - Mrs. Nick Katherine Jerefos, 1972 September 07; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-21)
  - Mrs. Emanuel Maurakis, 1973 January 04; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-22)
    Interviewed by Georgia Angelos. This audiotape has not been digitized and may be of poor sound quality.
  - Mrs. Stellios Pallios, 1973 March 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-24)
  - Mrs. Isidoros Kastanis, 1973 March 14; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-26)
  - Gust A. Kouris, 1973 January 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-30)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Mike S. Dragos, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-31)
  - Mike Lingos, 1974 May 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-32)
    Interviewed by H. Papanikolas and Nick Papanikolas. This audiotape has not been digitized and may be of poor sound quality.
  - Gus Papadakis, 1973 August 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-33)
    Interviewed by Zeese Papanikolas. This audiotape has not been digitized and may be of poor sound quality.
  - Mr. & Mrs. John Zekas, 1973 September 17; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-35)
  - Harry Greames, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-36)
  - Harry Greames, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-37)
  - Mrs. D. Georgelas and Melba Kouris, 1973 August; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-38)
  - Mrs. D. Georgelas and Melba Kouris, 1973 August; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-39)
  - George Georgelas, 1974 December 16; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Disc G-42)
    Interviewed by L. Cononelos. This audiotape has not been digitized and may be of poor sound quality.
  - Nina Ugenia Tsacopoulos Cononelos, 1974 June 27; Compact disc (Disc G-43)
    Interviewed by L. Cononelos
  - John Harry Mantas, 1974 December 09; Compact disc (Disc G-47)
  - Virginia Papahliou, 1974 December 02; Compact disc (Disc G-48)
  - George P. Papanikolas, 1974 December 02; Compact disc (Disc G-49)
  - George Leonudakis, 1974 June 28; Compact disc (Disc G-50)
  - Helen Skedros Rizos, 1974 November 20; Compact disc (Disc G-51)
  - James Velis (Velissaropoulos), 1974 December 11; Compact disc (Disc G-52)
  - Paraskevi Prekeges, 1974 June 26; Compact disc (Disc G-53)
  - Mrs. Josephine Bonacci, 1975 March 21; Compact disc (Disc G-54)
  - Mrs. Chasty Olsen Harris, undated; Compact disc (Disc G-55)
  - John Kotsouos, 1974 September 19; Compact disc (Disc G-56)
  - Peter Chris Argentos, 1974 December 04; Compact disc (Disc G-57)
  - Anast "Ernest" Chipian, undated; Compact disc (Disc G-58)
  - Mrs. Topa Lian, 1976 March 11; Compact disc (Disc G-59)
- Spanish oral histories, 1968-1973
  - Massari, undated; Compact disc (Disc S-2)
  - Maurice S. Cordova, undated; Compact disc (Disc S-8)
    Born 7 April 1926 in San Acacio, Luis, Colorado. Employee for Wlfare Seal department.
    Interviewed by John R. Tapia.
  - J. Guadalupe Garza, 1973 July 03; Compact disc (Disc S-45)
    Interviewed by Grey Coronada Jr.
  - Pedro Gonzalez Carranza, 1972 August 03; Compact disc (Disc S-48)
    Interviewed by Bernice P. Mertinez and Vincente Mayer.
  - Mr. & Mrs. Jimenez, 1972 June 19; Compact disc (Disc S-54)
    Interviewed by Margia Archuletta and Chuck Labato
  - Jose Jesus Palacis, 1972 June 13; Compact disc (Disc S-59)
    Interviewed by Margia Archuleta and Vince Mayer
  - Robert Cuellar, 1972 December 26; Compact disc (Disc S-62)
    Interviewed by Greg Coronado
  - Robert Cuellar, 1972 December 27; Compact disc (Disc S-63)
  - Mike Romero, 1973 February 17; Compact disc (Disc S-67)
    Interviewed by Donald Strauss
  - Charles Concino, undated; Compact disc (Disc S-69)
  - Mrs. Grace Dolce, 1968 May; Compact disc (Disc S-79)
    Interviewed by Bernice P. Martinez
  - The Orgins of the Aztecs. Western History Center lecture, 1973 July 15; Compact disc (Disc S-87)
    Interviewed by Professor Moreno
  - Cosme Chacón, 1973 July 15; Compact disc (Disc S-109)
    Interviewed by Bernice Martinez and Eva Natividad
  - Cosme Chacón, 1973 July 15; Compact disc (Disc S-110)
  - Greg Coronado, 1973 July 01; Compact disc (Disc S-127a)
    Interviewed by Richard Navarro
  - Richard Navarro, 1973 July 01; Compact disc (Disc S-127b)
  - Jose E. Martinez, 1973 July 07; Compact disc (Disc S-128)
  - Jose E. Martinez, 1973 July 07; Compact disc (Disc S-129)
  - Greg Coronado; Vincent Mayer, 1973 August 01; Compact disc (Disc S-132)
    Interviewed by Ricardo Barbero
  - Maurice S. Cordova, 1973 August 09; Compact disc (Disc S-161)
    Employee, Welfare Department, San Luis, Colorado.
    Interviewed by J. Tapia
  - Maurice S. Cordova, 1973 August 09; Compact disc (Disc S-162)
  - Father Jerald Merrill, 1971 December 31; Compact disc (Disc S-184)
    Chicano experience in Utah.
    Interviewed by Floyd O'Neil and J. Mayer
  - Pagosa Junction, CO, 1973 June 07; Compact disc (Disc S-200)
  - Cosme Chacón, 1973 July 15; Compact disc (Disc S-201)
- Japanese-American research project, 1966-1997
  - Joe Hanaya; Chieko H. Ogawa; Thomas Tomika Ogawa; Koe Hanaya, 1966 October 29; Compact disc (Disc JARP-22)
  - Side 1) Eijiro Kawamura; Tadashi nakata; Matajiro Watada; Katsukei Sakaguchi; Togo Nakano; Lee Murata; Reverand Y. Tamai. Side 2) Koe Hanaya, 1966 October 28; Compact disc (Disc JARP-23)
    Side 1: Disscusion of Buddhist church lounge.
    Side 2: Salt Lake City.
  - Koe Hanaya; Harry M. Eda, 1966 October 28; Compact disc (Disc JARP-24)
  - Harry M. Eda, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-25)
  - Koe Hanaya; Chicko H. Ogawa; Harry Hiyoza Kumagai; Rupert and Josie Hachiya; Elna Miya, Yukiko Kimura; Alice Kasai, 1966 October 29; Compact disc (Disc JARP-26)
  - Rupert and Josei Hachiya; Elna Miya; Yukiko Kimura; Alice Kasia, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-27)
  - Kama Toyota, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-28)
    Mine camper operator.
  - Shigao Tokunaga, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-29)
  - Toru Shimizu; Gin Namba; Nataju Ushio; Charles J. Umemura; Shigao Tokunaga, 1966 October 29; Compact disc (Disc JARP-30)
  - Terumasa Y. K. Miyagishima; H. Y. Enomota; Nake Miya; Kumakichi Endow; Heijiro Shiozowa; Sadahiko Oda; Gozo Shimada; Shichizo Takehashi; Tami Akisada; Take Uchida; Mrs. Tomoka Horton; Mrs. Kazuku Monobe; Mrs. Robert C. Hancock, 1967 November 16; Compact disc (Disc JARP-31)
    Ogden Japanese Union Church
  - Harry M. Eda; Ray R. Takada; Charles S. Kawakame; Yosh Amano; Frank Tamagama; Mary Kauakami; Shoza Niwa, 1967 January 13; Compact disc (Disc JARP-32)
  - Mrs. Kuniko Terasawa; Terry "Terumasa" Adachi; Alice Kasai; Mitsuko Sasaki; Nooki and Sakoe Kobayashi, 1966 October 29; Compact disc (Disc JARP-33)
  - Jiro Moshiyuki; Oaisuke Mijstake; Mataju Ushio; Bunzo Fujii, 1967 November 19; Compact disc (Disc JARP-34)
  - Reverand Ohata; Roy Nakatani; Mr. and Mrs. Mayeda; Gonai Yamaguchi; Kenzo Shiki; Mr. and Mrs. Yano; Y. Murakami; J. G. Miya; Kato Tashiokato; Mrs. Ise Kato; Mrs. Toriko Yei, 1967 November 15; Compact disc (Disc JARP-35)
  - Translation of JARP-35, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-35T)
  - Jiro Mochizuke; Mr. and Mrs. Hinokichi Kawaguchi; Kamasaku Miyagishima, 1967 November 19; Compact disc (Disc JARP-36)
  - Translation of JARP-36, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-36T)
  - Tosh Kano testimony, 1967 November 26; Compact disc (Disc JARP-37)
    Japanese Church of Christ.
  - Mrs. Kama Toyota, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-38)
    Translated by Reverand Shokai Kanai.
  - Mrs. Esther Hirasawa and Hird Yasukochi, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-39)
  - Mrs. Kiyo Kasai; Mrs. Toshiko Abe; Mrs. Y. Murakami; Mr. C. Kanomata; Mr. S. Wakamatsu; Mrs. Yori Endo; Mrs H. Y. Kawamura; Mrs. S. Inashima; Mrs. S. Yokota; Mrs. M Yamada, 1967 November 22; Compact disc (Disc JARP-40)
  - Sashichi S. Koyoma; E. A. Huntley; Henry Haijima Fujii; Mrs. Roy Abe; Mrs. S. Kawai; Takemaru Hirashara, 1966 October 21; Compact disc (Disc JARP-41)
  - Takemaru Hirahara; Henry Fujii; Mrs. Roy Abe; Mrs. S. Kawai; John Arime; Takashi Koyama, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-42)
  - Fakashi Koyama, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-43)
  - Richard Suenaga (Disc JARP-44)
  - Richard Suenaga, 1967 November 23; Compact disc (Disc JARP-45)
  - Johnny Kiyshi Saiki; Tomizo Miyamoto; Itsuki Hashimoto; Tatsuhei Tsuda, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-46)
  - Johnny Kiyoshi Saiki; Tommy Tadayoshi Shito; James Kuga; Robert A. Wilson; Haruko Kobayashi; Joe Grant Masaoka; Min Yasui; Sojiro Yoritomo, 1966 October 26; Compact disc (Disc JARP-47)
  - Hana Hayashi; Mrs. Tanta Kushibashi; Yusaburo Sakota; Mrs. Toki Sakata; Gontaro Kubota; Mrs. Kiyo Kuto, 1966 October 25; Compact disc (Disc JARP-48)
  - Phoebe Asano; Mrs. H. M. Otsuki; Reverand Hiram K. Kano, 1966 October 28; Compact disc (Disc JARP-49)
  - Shinkidri Tokunaga; Otsuji Kageyama; Inokidi Fukuda, 1966 November 12; Compact disc (Disc JARP-50)
    Held at Zadankai at Buddhist Church in Denver, Colorado in conjunction with the 50th anniversary commemoration.
  - Shinkidri Tokunaga; Otsuji Kageyama; Inokidi Fukuda; Harry Yukei Ujifusa, 1966 November 11; Compact disc (Disc JARP-51)
  - Sojiro Yoritomo; Fred Nobuichi Kawamura; Yoshitaka Tamai; Reverand Ryutetsu Kazumata, 1966 October 27; Compact disc (Disc JARP-52)
  - Reverand Jonathon Fujita; Dr. Frank E. Hayano, 1966 October 28; Compact disc (Disc JARP-53)
  - Heijiro nakano, 1966 November 13; Compact disc (Disc JARP-54)
  - Reverand Ryutetsu Kazumata; Susturo Nakamura, 1966 October 27; Compact disc (Disc JARP-55)
  - Reverand Noburu Tsunoda; Sakaguchi Katsuki; Nakata Tadashi; Matajiro Scishiro; Matajiro Watado; Shimita Nakano, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-56)
  - Conclusion of JARP-56, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-57)
  - Mrs. Kome Kosuge; George T. Fukuma; George Y. Inai; Roy M. Sueturo; Yuzo Honda; Misayo Mizoui, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-58)
  - Minoru Yasui, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-59)
  - Minoru Yasui, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-60)
  - Minoru Yasui, undated; Compact disc (Disc JARP-61)
  - William M. Marutani; Tosh Kano, 1967 November 25; Compact disc (Disc JARP-62)
    IDC Convention: recognition banquet, speakers William M. Marutani and Tosh Kano.
  - Mrs. Uno (Sasaki Umemura), 1997 November; Compact disc (Disc JARP-63)
  - Unknown oral history, 1967 November 16; Compact disc (Disc JARP-262a)
  - Unknown oral history, undated; Audiocassette (Cassette JARP-262b)
    Recording is in Japanese. No translation.
- Japanese Asian studies oral histories, 1972-1973
  - Toraji Koseki, 1972 April 30; Compact disc (Disc J-1)
    Interviewed by O'Neil, Parsons, and Aramaki
  - Toraji Koseki, 1972 April 30; Compact disc (Disc J-2)
  - Mrs. Kurumada, 1972 April 25; Compact disc (Disc J-3)
    Interviewed by Leslie Kurumada
  - Mrs. Masa Aramaki, 1972 April 16; Compact disc (Disc J-4)
    Interviewed by Diane Aramaki
  - Ron Aramaki, 1972 April; Compact disc (Disc J-5)
    Interviewed by F. O'Neil
  - Mrs. J. Goragi Kosebi, 1972 May 13; Compact disc (Disc J-6)
  - Mr. J. Goragi Kosebi, 1972 May 13; Compact disc (Disc J-7)
  - Koh Hinaya, 1972 May 12; Compact disc (Disc J-8)
    Interviewed by Ron Aramaki and F. O'Neil
  - Koh Hinaya, 1972 May 12; Compact disc (Disc J-9)
    Interviewed by Aramaki and O'Neil
  - T. Tadehara, 1972 May; Compact disc (Disc J-10)
    Interviewed by Steve Kido
  - Mrs. Ada (Iseko) Koseki, 1972 May 07; Compact disc (Disc J-11)
    Interviewed by Maxi Parsons
  - Alice Kasia, 1972 July 20; Compact disc (Disc J-12)
    Interviewed by Steve Kido and Bunny Matsumuja
  - Alice Kasai, 1972 July 20; Compact disc (Disc J-13)
  - Alice Kasai, 1972 July 26; Compact disc (Disc J-14)
  - Alice Kasai, 1972 July 26; Compact disc (Disc J-15)
  - Mrs. Takei Uchida, 1972 August 02; Compact disc (Disc J-16)
  - Toru Shimizu, 1972 August 09; Compact disc (Disc J-17)
  - Koe Hanoya, 1972 May 16; Compact disc (Disc J-18)
    Interviewed by Ron Aramaki
  - Koe Hanoya, 1972 May 16; Compact disc (Disc J-19)
  - Yasu Aramaki, 1972 April 19; Compact disc (Disc J-20)
  - Roy Takada, 1972 December 28; Compact disc (Disc J-21)
  - Untitled, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-22)
  - Untitled, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-23)
  - Untitled, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-24)
  - Untitled, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-25)
  - Untitled, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-26)
  - Untitled, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-27)
  - Untitled, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-28)
  - Untitled, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-29)
  - Untitled, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-30)
  - Untitled, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-31)
  - Untitled, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-32)
  - Alice Kasai; Mitsuko Sasaki; Nadine and Sakae Kobayushi, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-33)
  - Kuniko Terazawa; Daisuke Miyatake, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-34)
  - Unknown oral history, undated; Compact disc (Disc J-39)
  - Mrs. Chujo Matsumiya, 1973 May 27; Compact disc (Disc J-62)
    Interviewed by Bunny Matsumuja and Gail Matsumuja
  - Mrs. Uno, 1973 June 14; Compact disc (Disc J-63)
  - Mr. Goraji Koseki, 1973 June 19; Compact disc (Disc J-64)
  - Mr. Goraje; Joe Koseki, 1973 June 19; Compact disc (Disc J-65)
  - Harry Mori, 1973 June 21; Compact disc (Disc J-66)
  - Harry Mori, 1973 June 21; Compact disc (Disc J-67)
  - Jiro Mochizuki, 1973 June 21; Compact disc (Disc J-68)
    Interviewed by Al Oshita
  - Mrs. Riyo Okubo, 1973 June 24; Compact disc (Disc J-69)
  - Mrs. Riyo Okubo, 1973 June 24; Compact disc (Disc J-70)
  - Mrs. Sato Kawaguchi, 1973 June 19; Compact disc (Disc J-71)
  - Mrs. Thomas Ogawa, 1973 June 14; Compact disc (Disc J-72)
  - Mrs. Thomas Ogawa, 1973 June 14; Compact disc (Disc J-73)
  - Naka Shimizu, 1973 July 05; Compact disc (Disc J-74)
    Interviewed by Mari Parsons
  - Geechi Fukui (Issei), undated; Compact disc (Disc J-75)
    Interviewed by Kathy Ogura
  - Mr. Roy Okamoto, 1973 July 10; Compact disc (Disc J-76)
    Interviewed by Bunny Matsumuja
- Utah women's political oral history project, 1976-1991
  - Judge Reva Beck Basone, 1976 May 10; Compact disc (Disc UWP-1)
  - Judge Reva Beck Basone, 1976 May 14; Compact disc (Disc UWP-2)
  - Mrs. Beatrice Marchant, 1976 October 21; Compact disc (Disc UWP-3)
  - Nellie Jack, 1976 November 18; Compact disc (Disc UWP-4)
  - Eloise McQuown, undated; Compact disc (Disc UWP-5)
  - Susanna Mae Grua, 1977 March 31; Compact disc (Disc UWP-6)
  - Frances Farley, 1977 April 30; Compact disc (Disc UWP-7)
  - Eloise McQuown, 1977 May 18; Compact disc (Disc UWP-8)
  - Frances Farley, 1977 June 09; Compact disc (Disc UWP-9)
  - Sonia Johnson, 1991 September; Compact disc (Disc UWP-9b)
    Strategy session.
  - Unknown oral history, undated; Compact disc (Disc UWP-10)
  - Unknown oral history, undated; Compact disc (Disc UWP-11)
- Walker River oral histories, 1974
  - Bridget Harvy, 1974 January 24; Compact disc (Disc WR-1)
  - Stannard Frank, 1974 January 24; Compact disc (Disc WR-2)
  - Manuel McCloud, undated; Compact disc (Disc WR-3)
  - Sullivan Thom (Includes Christmas music from Sullivan Thom's private collection), 1974 April 15; Compact disc (Disc WR-4)
  - Edna Jones part 1, 1974 February 07; Compact disc (Disc WR-5)
  - Edna Jones part 2, 1974 February 07; Compact disc (Disc WR-5)
  - Edna Jones part 3, 1974 February 15; Compact disc (Disc WR-5)
  - Roy Higgins, 1974 February 13; Compact disc (Disc WR-6)
  - Edna Jones, 1974 February 21; Compact disc (Disc WR-7)
  - Edna Jones; Bert Summerfield, 1974 February 21; Compact disc (Disc WR-8)
  - Walter Voorhees, 1974 March 01; Compact disc (Disc WR-9)
  - Bob Johnson, 1974 March 15; Compact disc (Disc WR-10)
  - Walter Voorhees, 1974 March 01; Compact disc (Disc WR-11)
  - Walter Voorhees, 1974 March 01; Compact disc (Disc WR-12)
  - Walter Voorhees, 1974 March 01; Compact disc (Disc WR-13)
    Missing from collection
  - Walter Voorhees, 1974 March 13; Compact disc (Disc WR-14)
  - Agnes Sommaripa, 1974 April 28; Compact disc (Disc WR-15)
  - Virgil Boney, undated; Compact disc (Disc WR-16)
  - Mary Wilson, undated; Compact disc (Disc WR-17)
  - Popeye McCloud, 1974 March 12; Compact disc (Disc WR-18)
  - Rosie Quarty; Jennie Quintero; Gertie Holbrook; Frank John; Pete Snapp, undated; Compact disc (Disc WR-19)
  - Gertie Holbrook; Frank John; Pete Snapp, undated; Compact disc (Disc WR-20)
- Mexico oral history project, 1970-1971
  - Harvey H. Taylor, 1971 August 29; Compact disc (Disc MOHP-1)
  - Damiana Ponce, 1971 August 31; Compact disc (Disc MOHP-2)
  - Ambrosio Cabual, 1971 September 01; Compact disc (Disc MOHP-3)
  - Sra Manuela Soto Arieta, 1971 September 10; Compact disc (Disc MOHP-4)
  - Lucille B. Taylor, 1970 November 27; Compact disc (Disc MOHP-5)
  - Pedro Zapata Viscarra, 1970 November 29; Compact disc (Disc MOHP-6)
  - John Floyd Walser, 1970 November 30; Compact disc (Disc MOHP-7)
- Zuni land claim oral history project, 1986
  - Dr. Spencer O. Ellesworth, 1986 February 12; Compact disc (Disc ZLC-1)
  - Al Anderson, 1986 February 12; Compact disc (Disc ZLC-2)
  - Alex Scowtewa, 1986 February 13; Compact disc (Disc ZLC-3)
  - Alex Scowtewa, 1986 February 13; Compact disc (Disc ZLC-4)
  - Mrs. Mabel Hinkson, 1986 February 12; Compact disc (Disc ZLC-5)
  - M. Jay Platt, 1986 February 12; Compact disc (Disc ZLC-6)
  - Unknown oral history, 1986 February 04; Compact disc (Disc ZLC-7)
  - Unknown oral history, 1986 February 04; Compact disc (Disc ZLC-8)
  - Unknown oral history, undated; Compact disc (Disc ZLC-9)
- Westwood oral history project, 1987
  - Session 20, undated; Compact disc (Disc WW-1)
  - Session 21, undated; Compact disc (Disc WW-2)